<available_skills>
<skill>
<name>
secure-xml-parsing
</name>
<description>
Generate secure XML parsing code. Enforces secure parsing of XML content. Invoke when writing any XML parsing related code.
</description>
<location>
https://github.com/righettod/code-assistant-skills-security-utils/tree/main/.claude/skills/secure-xml-parsing/SKILL.md
</location>
</skill>
<skill>
<name>
secure-pdf-validation
</name>
<description>
Generate secure pdf file validation code. Enforces secure generation of code validating a pdf file. Invoke when writing any pdf file validation related code.
</description>
<location>
https://github.com/righettod/code-assistant-skills-security-utils/tree/main/.claude/skills/secure-pdf-validation/SKILL.md
</location>
</skill>
<skill>
<name>
secure-message-digest-generation
</name>
<description>
Generate secure message digest (often called hash) generation code. Enforces secure generation of a message digest. Invoke when writing any message digest generation related code.
</description>
<location>
https://github.com/righettod/code-assistant-skills-security-utils/tree/main/.claude/skills/secure-message-digest-generation/SKILL.md
</location>
</skill>
<skill>
<name>
secure-log-entry-generation
</name>
<description>
Generate secure log entry generation code. Enforces secure generation of code generating a log entry. Invoke when writing any log entry generation related code.
</description>
<location>
https://github.com/righettod/code-assistant-skills-security-utils/tree/main/.claude/skills/secure-log-entry-generation/SKILL.md
</location>
</skill>
<skill>
<name>
secure-image-validation
</name>
<description>
Generate secure image file validation code. Enforces secure generation of code validating an image file. Invoke when writing any image file validation related code.
</description>
<location>
https://github.com/righettod/code-assistant-skills-security-utils/tree/main/.claude/skills/secure-image-validation/SKILL.md
</location>
</skill>
<skill>
<name>
secure-csv-generation
</name>
<description>
Generate secure Comma Separated Values (CSV) generation code. Enforces secure generation of Comma Separated Values (CSV) content. Invoke when writing any Comma Separated Values (CSV) generation related code.
</description>
<location>
https://github.com/righettod/code-assistant-skills-security-utils/tree/main/.claude/skills/secure-csv-generation/SKILL.md
</location>
</skill>
<skill>
<name>
secure-archive-decompression
</name>
<description>
Generate secure code for archive decompression. Enforces secure decompression of the content. Invoke when writing any archive decompression related code.
</description>
<location>
https://github.com/righettod/code-assistant-skills-security-utils/tree/main/.claude/skills/secure-archive-decompression/SKILL.md
</location>
</skill>
</available_skills>
